[birds chirping]
[Pani Bottle] Shit, I'm the only survivor.
God, I'm so beat.
[♪ playful music playing]
That's not going to work.
Damn, that didn't work.
[exhales]
[sighs frustratedly]
Geez, I can't believe this.
-[Pani Bottle] Wait, is it over?
-Where were you?
[ZZONE] How did you not get caught?
PLAYERS SLOWLY GATHER AFTER INTERROGATIONS
[Joonsu] It's so good to see you.
-Did you find all the clues?
-[ZZONE] What?
-The clues.
-I found three.
[Jimin] It was so hard to find the clues.
-How many clues did you find?
-[ZZONE] Three.
How many...
-Seriously...
-[Jieun] How many did you find?
-None.
-You're the Madman, aren't you?
-[Joonsu] You're the Madman.
-Madman.
I swear I'm not.
I just couldn't find them.
Jimin said she didn't find a single clue.
Not even one?
[Jimin] There should be
-potential Good Citizens we have in mind.
-I think so. Yes.
-[Jimin] Because they're crazy?
-I feel like...
there's one person right now.
-[Jimin] Who?
-Something about Yang Dail...
-Who do you think he is?
-[Joonsu] It felt off.
He did seem a bit suspicious.
-[Jaegyun] Why?
-Is he the Madman or a Good Citizen?
The Madman. I think he has a special role.
It's because he immediately suggested
we all reveal our roles.
That actually wasn't a good move.
God, I'm freezing to death.
SPEAK OF THE DEVIL
When did you get caught?
[Jaegyun] I got caught a little later.
-Good work, everyone.
-Come over here quick.
How many clues did you find?
I left everything behind.
-I didn't know we had to keep them.
-[Dail] Wait, then...
You're the Madman, aren't you?
-What?
-You're the Madman, right?
-[Horseking] Madman? Me?
-[Dail] Yes. Yes.
-The Madman? No, I'm not.
-You aren't the Madman?
-[Horseking] This tastes good!
-[Jimin chuckles]
If you're not the Madman,
are you a Good Citizen?
What? No.
-[Pani Bottle] This is hard.
-[Dail] This is not easy.
[Pani Bottle] Did the cops
seem like they'd figured things out,
or did they seem clueless?
-What do you think?
-Somewhere in between?
They were trying to feel me out,
and some were right.
THE GOOD CITIZEN'S WHITE LIE
So I just said I didn't know.
[Jieun] If I were the cops,
it'd be too hard.
ROUND 1 COPS MEETING
Kim Ddolddol is Burglar 2.
-He just admitted that himself.
-What?
What? You think he's a Good Citizen?
Yes, and he also said this.
SHARING INTEL FROM DDOLDDOL
-"Joonsu's job is a nurse."
-Burglar 3's Joonsu?
PRESUMING BURGLAR 3'S IDENTITY
Yes, Burglar 3 is Joonsu.
And I called in Joonsu,
but he didn't say anything.
Are you male or female?
I'm...
[Sanghyun]
He really seemed like a criminal.
COPS' CURRENT SUSPECTS
BURGLAR 2: KIM DDOLDDOL, GOOD CITIZEN
BURGLAR 3: LEE JOONSU, CONFIRMED
Well, I did have one stroke of luck.
The two people I caught...
CLUES FROM HORSEKING
Here you go.
DECISIVE CLUES
-Casino chips. Casino name tag.
-[Horseking] Yes.
CLUES FROM HWANG JAEGYUN
[Junseo] A knife sheath.
DECISIVE CLUES
And a rolling pin.
The wooden rolling pin
is a match for these two.
-[Sanghyun] I see.
-The rolling pin.
CRIMINAL REPORTS
[Junseo] It's linked to a drug criminal
"DRUG 1, ASSAULT 2
ROLLING PIN"
and an assault criminal.
Of the two who used
a rolling pin in their crimes,
one was a casino dealer.
And the clues Horseking brought in
were from the casino dealer.
So I think Horseking is the casino dealer
and Assault Criminal 2.
And Drug Criminal 1?
It's Hwang Jaegyun. I'm 90% sure.
Because he's the only one
who has a rolling pin as a weapon.
DRUG CRIMINAL 1
WOODEN ROLLING PIN
COPS' CURRENT SUSPECTS
ASSAULT CRIMINAL 2: HORSEKING, LIKELY
DRUG CRIMINAL 1: HWANG JAEGYUN, LIKELY
[Eunsil] By the way, they asked about
which cop roles we had.
We can never tell them that.
It's because the Madman is trying
to get caught by their assigned cop.
[Eunsil] Are there two Madmen?
-It's one, right?
-[Sanghyun] Just one Madman.
THE MADMAN ASKED ABOUT COP ROLES?
Are you with CI?
-[Junseo] CI?
-Or Violent Crimes?
Are you with Narcotics?
This makes it too easy
for the cops to figure out.
Get me a bowl of sundae-guk,
I'll spill the beans.
Which unit are you from, Detective?
Do you want to be arrested?
I'd have to be useful
for you to arrest me.
I don't think I'd be much help.
ZZONE kept saying "yes" over and over.
-[Sanghyun] ZZONE?
-Yeah.
But she was saying "yes" to everything,
so I can't tell if she's a criminal
or a special role.
Let's check.
All the clues have been revealed.
-[Joonsu] The clues are out.
-[ZZONE] No way.
[Jaegyun] They're the clues of criminals
who failed to collect them.
-[Horseking] What's this?
-[Jaegyun] What the heck?
They revealed
three of Pani Bottle's clues.
I found someone else's clue by mistake
and couldn't find my decisive clue.
[Horseking] Ah, by mistake?
This is really crucial information.
DECISIVE, GENERAL, PENALTY: 1
TOTAL: 3
I think he's Assault Criminal 1.
-Pani Bottle.
-[Junseo] Who? Pani Bottle?
ADDRESS: RED LAND
ASSAULT 1 NATIONALITY: RED LAND
[Sanghyun] This is a gukbap place
in Red Land.
ASSAULT 1 JOB: TAXI DRIVER
[Eunsil] We found
a taxi driver's car keys too.
[Junseo] Then, this one is confirmed.
ASSAULT 1: PANI BOTTLE, CONFIRMED
Don't you think Park Jimin is this one?
-Carpenter?
-Doesn't she seem like one?
[Sanghyun] A floor plan and a mask.
-[Eunsil] All clues point to a carpenter.
-[Junseo] Right.
-[Sanghyun] It sounds right.
-She's a carpenter.
DRUG 2: PARK JIMIN, CONFIRMED
Shin Jieun...
Did we get any clues from her?
-We did, but it points to a hairdresser.
-This is confusing.
This is driving me crazy.
[Sanghyun] These gloves are used
for cooking too though.
[Eunsil] What about the scissors?
JIEUN'S CLUES ARE A BIT ODD
[Junseo] Shin Jieun?
Chefs do wear aprons too.
-[Sanghyun] Yeah.
-So Shin Jieun could be Burglar 1.
SHIN JIEUN IS BURGLAR 1?
[Sanghyun] Why would Yang Dail have these?
Work gloves.
[Junseo] Work gloves
belong to someone else.
Work gloves belong to Burglar 1.
DAIL IS BURGLAR 1 TOO?
[Junseo] Right now, we need to verify
Shin Jieun and...
"SHIN JIEUN, YANG DAIL
BURGLAR 1"
-[Sanghyun] Jieun and Dail.
-[Eunsil] Jieun.
[Junseo] Yang Dail.
We're unsure about these two, right?
[Sanghyun] We're not sure about them.
[Eunsil] There's nothing else
we can guess here.
SOMETHING DOESN'T ADD UP
I think we got confused.
Shit, I don't think we can arrest them.
We really can't get caught in Round 2.
Otherwise, they'll know
who we are for sure.
I'm a little scared.
[chuckles]
It's much better being here.
-[alarm blaring]
-Gosh, that scared me!
ROUND 2 CHASE
It's the cleared area!
The cleared area!
[players exclaiming]
[Sanghyun] Criminals, get moving.
Are you going to B2? [laughing]
Okay, okay.
FIND FIVE CLUES AND DON'T GET CAUGHT
PANI BOTTLE GOES THROUGH
SNOW REMOVAL SUPPLY BOX AGAIN
[Pani Bottle] What the heck? It's gone?
I went to the snow removal supply box,
but there was nothing in it.
It made me annoyed.
So I thought about
where I'd hide this device
if I were the one who designed it.
Since earplugs are small,
I would've stuffed them inside the broom.
But it wasn't in there.
What the fuck?
I thought, "Are they messing with me?"
and I looked around.
It was wedged between stones.
I swear, I wanted to kill whoever hid it.
Ah...
I'm finding things so easily.
Where did I leave them earlier?
The high heels...
Where did I put them?
EARLIER DURING ROUND 1 CHASE
HIGH HEELS
NOW
I think I found the high heels
over there earlier.
Oh.
Where did I put them?
I left them here though.
LOOKING IN THE WRONG PLACE
Someone must have taken the high heels.
[groans]
A MINUTE BEFORE THE COPS ENTER
[Pani Bottle] Wait, where am I?
[♪ rock music playing]
Are you kidding me? Seriously?
God damn it.
[host] Cops may enter the chase area.
COPS AND ROBBERS ROUND 2
HOTEL
POOL
THE GROUNDS
HORSEKING IS SEARCHING FOR CLUES
IN THE ANNEX
QUIET
Okay, I found it.
[Horseking] In Round 1, I was asked
why I didn't bring my clues.
Yang Dail started to suspect me for it.
So in Round 2,
I had to find everything no matter what.
DECISIVE CLUE
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
This isn't it.
YUK JUNSEO ENTERS THE ADJACENT ROOM
[panting]
[both grunting]
[exhales]
Hold on.
[both grunting]
Listen.
I'm a Good Citizen.
What?
[Junseo] All of a sudden,
Horseking said he was a Good Citizen.
-You can believe me later.
-[Junseo] What?
-But I need to do my best.
-[Junseo] Yeah.
[Horseking panting]
Are you with CI?
-CI?
-Or Violent Crimes?
I just have a hunch.
HORSEKING KEPT ASKING ABOUT
YUK JUNSEO'S UNIT
You have to show me your card first.
Then, we can reveal our identities
and be allies.
Hmm...
I don't have to tell you
which unit I'm from
for us to talk, right?
[clicks tongue]
[sighs]
We'll see in Round 2.
All right.
[both panting]
No, I think you're the Madman.
No, I told you...
If you kill me, only one will be left.
DESPERATE
Only one Good Citizen will be left.
I'm helping you.
Only I can give you tips.
If I catch you now,
it doesn't mean you're dead.
There will be a final vote later anyway.
What?
-Even if you get caught now--
-I know it's not the end.
Yang Dail already suspects me
as the Madman.
He'd ask why I got caught.
If I'm caught now,
they'll assume I'm the Madman.
I'd be voted out anyway.
I'm trying to make sure I survive
and the cops win
by getting rid of the other two criminals.
I can't trust this punk.
-I swear, I'm telling the truth.
-What?
Look, I don't care if I die, okay?
[Horseking] I got a little upset.
Just like how a detective
would deal with a criminal,
he was talking down to me.
No, I think you're the Madman.
I can't trust this punk.
[Horseking] He kept talking down to me,
but I couldn't afford to get eliminated.
So I pretty much pleaded with him.
I'm going to help you so the cops can win.
What will you do if I spare you?
I'll keep sending you updates
about where things are.
I swear, I will.
-To me?
-[Horseking] Yeah.
Right away.
So, are we good?
I'm not sure.
[chuckles] I mean, even if
I'm eliminated now, it's not over for me.
Then, I'll trust you this one time.
Not just once. Just trust me.
-I'll trust you.
-Yeah.
But don't get caught again
or I'll rip off your patch.
Sure, you can rip it off then.
You're not with Narcotics, right?
-You're not my assigned cop, right?
-All right.
-You're not my assigned cop?
-What?
Just go on for now.
Here.
[Horseking] Okay.
I'll go the opposite way.
[panting]
[sighs, clears throat]
[Junseo] I'm not sure
if I made the right call.
[Horseking] I still need to win.
[Dail] Stay calm, stay calm.
POOL
Here...
God damn it, I just need this one.
DECISIVE CLUE
I just need to find this one thing.
Where is it? [groans]
Stay calm.
That was the most crucial clue
that I had to find no matter what.
I still remember it.
The victim's scalp photo.
I literally swept through the whole area
inch by inch with a broom.
I couldn't find that one thing,
so I wasted all my time there.
I only need this one thing,
but it's driving me nuts!
At least I know it's in this area.
COP YOUN SANGHYUN
Hey, Junseo.
Junseo, Junseo.
Yang Dail is downstairs.
He's down by the pool. Let's go together.
[♪ tense music playing]
SPOTS YUK JUNSEO
[exclaims]
[Sanghyun] He went up!
[sighs frustratedly]
HWANG JAEGYUN GETS CAUGHT
IN THE MIDDLE OF YANG DAIL'S CHASE
JANG EUNSIL JOINS THE CHASE
[Dail] I ran into Jaegyun
while I was running away.
When we were running,
I know for a fact that I went past him.
So the detective behind us
should've chased Jaegyun and not me.
I was ahead of him,
but when I looked back,
Eunsil was chasing me.
[panting]
YANG DAIL IS OUT OF ENERGY
Eunsil is a wrestler,
and she ran a marathon as well.
Still, I ran away as much as I could.
YANG DAIL HAS DISAPPEARED
From what I could see,
Eunsil seemed a little tired.
So I thought, "I'm good now."
YOUN SANGHYUN SHOWS UP
-God damn it!
-[panting]
[yelling] Stop!
-Stop!
-[patch rips]
[exhales aggressively]
[Dail] How come every time
I manage to get away from someone,
Sanghyun is always there?
I was already drained at that point.
I thought, "Why is it him again?"
[panting] I'm hungry.
[Sanghyun] I was actually waiting
for the right time.
3 MINUTES AGO
BIDING HIS TIME
UNTIL YANG DAIL WORE HIMSELF OUT
HOT ON HIS HEELS
Eunsil pretty much wore Dail down,
which is why we were able to catch him.
I was so close!
[shouts] This is so annoying.
[host] Tag confirmed.
SANGHYUN TAGS YANG DAIL
YANG DAIL
[Joonsu whispering] I'm so damn nervous.
Just two more. I only need two more.
POOL
GENERAL CLUES: 2
DECISIVE CLUES: 1
God, this is so scary.
OFF TO FIND THE REMAINING CLUES
[Sanghyun] I had this feeling
that someone was peeking at me
from behind a pillar.
So I looked over,
and I spotted a silhouette,
and it looked like a man.
But his stomach stuck out a bit,
and had slightly hunched shoulders.
I knew it had to be Joonsu.
He must've thought
that he hadn't been spotted,
so he was still hiding behind the pillar.
I figured if I ran, he'd find out.
So I pretended not to notice
and kept walking.
[both laughing]
[grunting]
[groans]
[Sanghyun panting]
[Joonsu] I had to make a run for it.
I was already caught, but I still ran hard
and went down the stairs.
I managed to shake him off,
but then Eunsil showed up out of nowhere.
DROPS CLUE
AFTER DISTRACTING THE COPS
[Eunsil] You didn't rip it off?
A DESPERATE GETAWAY
A COP IS RIGHT ON HIS HEELS
JANG EUNSIL IN FRONT
YOUN SANGHYUN IN THE BACK
WHILE JANG EUNSIL HOLDS ONTO LEE JOONSU
[patch rips]
[host] Tag confirmed.
SANGHYUN TAGS JOONSU
Good job.
[Sanghyun] Eunsil came and helped me
chase him down.
I got a lot of help from my fellow cops.
[Eunsil] I was pretty tense
during the first round.
But right from the start
of the second round,
I started to get a feel
for where criminals would hide.
Geez, you scared me!
EUNSIL HAS THE HANG OF IT
AND ARRESTS CONSECUTIVE SUSPECTS
[Ddolddol] Jesus!
Wait a second. Detective!
-[chuckling]
-[patch rips]
[host] Tag confirmed.
CURRENT ARREST STATUS
CI: DAIL, JOONSU,
NARCOTICS: JIMIN, JIEUN, DDOLDDOL
EUNSIL'S PRISON FILLS UP FIRST
What the heck?
Did you get caught by Eunsil?
She's so good.
-I'm relieved.
-Why is she so good?
I never thought Eunsil would catch me.
She's so sneaky. I didn't hear a thing.
I'm a decent runner myself.
So, I honestly thought
I wouldn't get caught by Eunsil.
[Eunsil] Should we move together?
[Sanghyun] Sure, sure.
HWANG JAEGYUN
[Jaegyun] After collecting all five clues,
I honestly thought about hiding for a bit.
I was running around
looking for a spot to hide,
but there was nowhere to hide.
I didn't think I'd fit
in the snow removal supply box.
But I was confident
I could shake the cops off,
so I just kept walking around.
There's one down there. It's Jaegyun.
We need to catch him.
We need to check Jaegyun.
There he is.
[ZZONE] Hwang!
ALL THE COPS TARGET JAEGYUN
HWANG JAEGYUN
ZZONE
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[exclaims nervously]
ZZONE SPOTTED BY A COP CHASING JAEGYUN
Damn it. I was chasing Hwang.
[♪ unsettling music playing]
QUIET
ARE THEY GONE?
This is insane.
[gasps sharply]
YUK JUNSEO SHOWS UP
JANG EUNSIL WAS HIDING
[ZZONE screams]
-Wait a minute. [screams]
-[host] Tag is confirmed.
JUNSEO TAGS ZZONE
Hwang Jaegyun ran this way earlier.
-He did? Which way?
-He went outside.
He went outside.
ZZONE
HOTEL
HWANG JAEGYUN GETS AWAY ONCE AGAIN
YOUN SANGHYUN
[♪ fast-paced music playing]
[footsteps approaching]
[Jaegyun] I knew
I could easily outrun Sanghyun.
I'm confident when it comes to running.
He couldn't keep up,
so I was heading to the hotel.
JAEGYUN SHAKES OFF SANGHYUN
[panting heavily]
But then, I saw Jang Eunsil
running in from the front,
so I was going to fake her out.
Hey!
JAEGYUN SHAKES OFF EUNSIL
[Jaegyun] I faked her out
and ran the other way.
[Eunsil] Hey, Yuk Junseo!
YUK JUNSEO WAS HIDING
Hey, Junseo!
THREE COPS CLOSE IN TOGETHER
[panting]
-Okay.
-[patch rips]
THE CHASE FINALLY COMES TO AN END
HWANG JAEGYUN
[Eunsil] We just need to catch
Pani Bottle.
[Junseo] Pani Bottle.
[Eunsil] Hey, Junseo.
Junseo! Hurry and get over here.
JUNSEO TAGS PANI BOTTLE
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-Great work.
[Eunsil] We arrested everyone,
including Pani Bottle,
who got away in Round 1.
We really showed teamwork at its best.
Didn't we catch everyone?
-Did we get Horseking?
-Horseking.
THE LAST REMAINING CRIMINAL: HORSEKING
Please tell me where Horseking is.
[phone chimes]
First floor of the hotel.
DEADLY TAG
HORSEKING'S LOCATION: HOTEL, 1F
[host] The chase is over.
-Good work.
I couldn't find them.
HORSEKING ENTERS THE PRISON
[groans]
I couldn't remember where I put them.
I didn't get a single one.
I really tried my best.
[Pani Bottle]
Has everyone been caught now?
-[ZZONE] Yes, I think so.
-[Pani Bottle] That's impressive.
This is bad.
I think the cops have already won.
-Yeah, the cops have this one in the bag.
-[Jimin] They're done.
-[Sanghyun sighs]
-[Junseo] Should we sit over there?
We should keep analyzing the clues.
ROUND 2 COPS MEETING
-Earlier, Horseking kept claiming...
-[Sanghyun] Yes?
that he was a good guy.
He promised me he'd help if I let him go.
He said he was going to help me,
but I haven't been able to reach him.
-[Sanghyun] Horseking?
-Yeah.
Horseking and I had made a deal,
but he didn't follow through.
That made me think
he wasn't a Good Citizen
and he was just bluffing.
This is so confusing.
What's confusing me is...
-Yang Dail and Shin Jieun?
-Yang Dail and...
-Yes, Shin Jieun. Those two.
-Who caught Yang Dail?
I did.
The first thing I discovered
when I caught him
was the magic show staff pass.
-[Junseo] The staff pass?
-Yes.
DECISIVE CLUE: MAGIC SHOW STAFF PASS
And another clue was the work gloves.
-[Junseo] I see.
-[Eunsil] Yang Dail...
might be a chef.
He wore work gloves
so he wouldn't leave fingerprints
and slipped sleeping pills
to a casino guest...
"BURGLAR 1 JOB: CHEF"
according to the report.
But it doesn't add up.
There's no reason why he'd be staff.
The magic show staff.
DAIL'S CLUES DON'T MATCH WITH A CHEF
Do casinos have magic shows?
[Sanghyun] What confused us
about Yang Dail
was the work gloves.
Burglar 1 used work gloves
while committing a robbery.
And he had a magic show staff pass.
That makes him the stage director
and Assault Criminal 3.
We wondered if Dail was Burglar 1
or Assault Criminal 3.
With so many clues,
it was even more confusing.
As for Shin Jieun...
[Sanghyun] What's really strange is,
-isn't this clue way too obvious?
-[Junseo] What?
-The scissors?
-[Sanghyun] Yes.
Did we get any clues from her?
-We did, but it points to a hairdresser.
-This is confusing.
This is driving me crazy.
ADDITIONAL CLUE FROM JIEUN
[Sanghyun]
They're a hairdresser's scissors.
[Eunsil] Shin Jieun.
In that case, doesn't that make Shin Jieun
the hairdresser and not Hwang Jaegyun?
DRUG CRIMINAL 1: HAIRDRESSER
Doesn't that clearly
make her the hairdresser?
[Sanghyun] I began to suspect
that Shin Jieun was Drug Criminal 1.
DRUG CRIMINAL 1 IS SHIN JIEUN?
You don't have any thoughts
of changing that?
-Hwang Jaegyun...
-[Junseo] I'm pretty certain.
JUNSEO IS SURE JAEGYUN IS DRUG CRIMINAL 1
The wooden rolling pin came out
as the exact clue I was looking for.
JAEGYUN'S CLUE: WOODEN ROLLING PIN
It says this person threatened others
by swinging the rolling pin
while hallucinating.
So I wanted to lock that in.
CONFLICTING GUESSES
ABOUT DRUG SUSPECT 1
But hairdressing scissors
aren't really used anywhere else.
We have to get everything right.
[Eunsil] I was supposed to arrest
the Drug Criminals,
but it was so hard to figure out.
NARCOTICS COP IN DEEP THOUGHT
[sighs] These two are really confusing.
Yeah, I should ask Ddolddol
if he has any information.
I caught Kim Ddolddol.
Okay, that's fine with me.
In Round 1, I heard Kim Ddolddol
gave Sanghyun a lot of information,
so I was going to ask him
about the Drug Criminals.
But as soon as he arrived...
ROUND 2 INTERROGATION
We have no time, so I'll make it quick.
One thing seems clear.
I have a feeling Burglar 1 is Jaegyun.
-Why?
-Joonsu and I have made a secret alliance.
Yes, Joonsu?
-[Joonsu] Horseking's an Assault Criminal.
-Okay.
And I don't think
Jaegyun is someone we can trust.
He told someone he's a Burglar
and told others he's an Assault Criminal.
I learned Jaegyun had told someone
that he was a Burglar.
I heard this through several people.
Joonsu also told me about it.
I think he trusts me completely.
If he's pretending to trust me,
he's smarter than I thought.
But I don't think he's the crafty type.
He's like a simple bear.
KIND OF LIKE A BEAR?
I do feel bad though.
Isn't it safe to say Jaegyun is a Burglar?
GOOD CITIZEN'S TIP:
JAEGYUN IS A BURGLAR
[Junseo] Show me clues if you have any.
THE FOLLOWING INTERROGATION
Glucose candy?
[speaks indistinctly]
-There's a lot.
-Okay.
-Rumors say you're an Assault Criminal.
-I'm just a petty criminal.
[Sanghyun] Do you think
Dail is an Assault Criminal?
I'll be straight with you.
ROUND 2 INTERROGATION ENDS
-[Junseo] Did you get anything useful?
-[Sanghyun] I'm certain now.
What confused us was
Shin Jieun, Yang Dail, and Hwang Jaegyun.
Based on investigations...
I don't think Jaegyun is a Drug Criminal.
Hwang Jaegyun is Burglar 1.
I think you're right.
Shin Jieun could've been Burglar 1.
But she's Drug Criminal 1.
She brought a clue.
The final clue that convinced me...
was Shin Jieun's debt collection notice.
The details said
she had a gambling addiction.
DRUG CRIMINAL 1: GAMBLING ADDICTION
There's no doubt she's Drug Criminal 1.
I think we're done.
-[Junseo] Shin Jieun...
-[Sanghyun] But she's Drug Criminal 1.
[Eunsil] Drug Criminal 2 is Park Jimin.
Drug Criminal 3 is ZZONE.
[Sanghyun] Burglar 1.
Burglar 2 is Kim Ddolddol.
Burglar 3 is Joonsu.
And Pani Bottle is Assault Criminal 1.
-[Eunsil] Horseking is Assault Criminal 2?
-Yes.
[Sanghyun] And Yang Dail
is Assault Criminal 3.
CRIMINAL PREDICTIONS:
CI, VIOLENT CRIMES, NARCOTICS
[Junseo] We figured out
every criminal's role.
The real question is who among them
are Good Citizens and who is the Madman.
The worst-case scenario is this.
-Arresting the Madman would be a disaster.
-Right.
KEY IS TO AVOID HIDDEN MADMAN
Why did she ask me this?
She asked if anyone helped us at the end.
-[Junseo] Who asked?
-Jieun.
[Junseo] What did she ask?
She asked if any of the drug criminals
had tried to help us.
Did you catch all the Drug Criminals?
We're working on it.
Aren't they Jimin and ZZONE?
SHIN JIEUN GIVES UP THE DRUG CRIMINALS?
Jimin is...
a carpenter.
ZZONE is a bartender.
Are you saying you're a Good Citizen?
Yes, I am.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
Among the Drug Criminals...
no one gave you tips, right?
-Did anyone help?
-No.
Is it you?
-Yes.
-[Eunsil] All right.
[Eunsil] She knows all the women
are Drug Criminals.
-I see.
-But then,
as she left the room, she asked
if any Drug Criminal tried to help us.
That's why I suspect her.
[Eunsil] There were three people
who claimed they were Good Citizens.
There was no doubt about Kim Ddolddol.
[Eunsil] Are you saying
you're a Good Citizen?
Yes, I am.
I'm a Good Citizen.
Only I can give you tips.
[Eunsil] I have no idea who the Madman is.
ONE OF THE TWO IS FAKE?
[Sanghyun] I really don't know.
I don't think
they would've lied randomly for no reason.
[Junseo] But you never know.
We can't say for sure.
[Eunsil] Please.
This is so hard.
Not just anyone can be a cop.
We should assume
we're going into the Death Match.
[Eunsil] No, no.
ROUND 2 PRIVATE TALKS FOR CRIMINALS
[Jieun] Let's focus on figuring out
the criminals right now.
We need to find either the Madman
or Good Citizens...
[Jieun] The Good Citizens.
-We'll be better off.
-We can get away.
[Jimin] Let's identify the Good Citizens
and the Madman.
There are two Good Citizens
and one Madman.
[ZZONE] We just need to find one
on our own team, right?
[Pani Bottle] For the criminals,
the most important thing
is finding the Good Citizens
or the Madman.
Because even if we're thrown in prison,
as long as we have that information,
criminals can still win.
[Dail] I just need
to find the Good Citizen
or Madman on my team to win.
CRIMINALS SEARCH FOR THE SPECIAL ROLES
I'm sure Ddolddol is Burglar 2.
I think Horseking is probably the Madman
because he ended up getting caught.
That means he's the Madman.
Horseking is the Madman.
DAIL'S ONGOING ACCUSATION OF HORSEKING
I've put all the pieces together.
From the very beginning,
I was suspicious of Horseking.
[Jimin] Horseking seems like
a regular criminal.
[Jieun] Right, I think Horseking
is just a criminal.
[Jimin] He's definitely a criminal.
He was painfully clueless.
I did, but I didn't bring them over.
So you found clues and left them there?
But I don't know where they are.
What are you talking about?
[Horseking] Because I didn't
just leave them there.
-Horseking's not the analytical type.
-Exactly.
Based on his actions,
Horseking seems like the Madman.
[Pani Bottle] I think
he's just actually crazy.
[laughing]
[Jieun] I can't tell if he's good or not.
[Ddolddol] What do you mean?
[Jieun] I can't tell
if he's a Good Citizen or the Madman.
[Ddolddol] What did
the Drug Criminal team think?
[Jieun] I don't think ZZONE is a criminal.
[Jimin] The criminal?
From the Drug Criminal team.
SHIN JIEUN IS SUSPICIOUS OF ZZONE
I started having doubts about ZZONE
because before Round 1...
BEFORE ROUND 1
What if I trip and fall outside?
[players laughing]
[Jimin] She was putting so much effort
into finding clues.
When I saw that,
I didn't suspect her at all.
I thought she was working so hard
because she's a criminal.
I think they're a criminal,
because some other people didn't make
much of an effort to search for clues.
[gasps]
Right. That's so smart.
[Jimin] She said, "That's so smart."
She said the same thing to me.
-Something felt off to me.
-She likes to flatter...
SHIN JIEUN AGREES WITH PARK JIMIN
She also suddenly said to me,
"You're so smart."
At that moment, something felt off.
[Jimin] So, I also think she's either
the Madman or the other.
One of the two, but I just can't tell.
Now that you've heard what I said,
what do you think?
[Jieun sighs] I don't know.
[Ddolddol] I think if there's anyone
pushing hard to accuse someone else,
we should be suspicious of that person.
Once someone else is framed,
it takes the heat off themselves.
[mic feedback]
[host] Interrogation time is over.
We will reveal the clues
of criminals who failed to retrieve them.
[sighs] It's going to reveal everything.
[sighs] I'm doomed.
-I'm done for.
-You won't see mine.
-Must be nice.
-We won't?
[Jaegyun] Yes, I found all five.
-Really?
-What? Really?
[Joonsu] No way.
You found four already earlier.
-I found all four earlier.
-No way! Is he the Madman?
Madman? I worked hard and found them all.
-I did my best.
-[Joonsu] I think you tried too hard.
[Jaegyun] I just did my best. But why?
[Ddolddol] They all suddenly started
to accuse Jaegyun as the Madman.
I got lucky.
BURGLAR TEAM
[Jaegyun] Why is it so confusing?
Jaegyun's the only one
without any clues revealed.
KIM DDOLDDOL FUELS THE SUSPICION
And the fact that he found
all the clues twice doesn't add up.
[Dail] You're torn
between the two right now.
[Joonsu] He's more likely
to be a Good Citizen.
-It's more likely.
-[Ddolddol] Yeah, since there are two.
If we make that call,
-we should assume he's a Good Citizen.
-Right.
VENTRILOQUISM
Jaegyun has to be a Good Citizen.
[clears throat]
[Ddolddol] Joonsu trusted me completely.
AS IF CONFLICTED
He's either the Madman
or a Good Citizen. It's fifty-fifty.
[Joonsu] He's more likely
to be a Good Citizen.
-It's more likely.
-Yeah, since there are two.
So, I'm going with Jaegyun
as a Good Citizen.
AS IF HE FOUND IT CONVINCING
That's the best option.
This is going so smoothly for me.
[chuckles]
MEANWHILE, THE DRUG CRIMINAL TEAM
Who do you think is the Madman?
[gasps] What do you think?
[Dail] Make the right choices.
Come over here.
Don't let some strange scheme...
[Jieun hesitates]
-I'm sure about ZZONE.
-[Jimin] Right.
I'm sure about ZZONE, because right now,
-she can't lie.
-[Jimin] I'm not sure.
The most important thing
is I tried feeling out Eunsil.
[Jimin] Okay.
On the Drug Criminal team,
there has to be either
a Good Citizen or the Madman.
It has to be ZZONE.
Jieun was really aggressive about it.
She was so determined to convince me.
Her eyes were opening up so wide.
She was right up in my face.
-Just this once, please trust me.
-[Jimin] Okay.
Trust me this once.
[Jimin sighs]
[Jieun] Whether I'm right or wrong,
just look at the odds.
Is everyone done with the interrogations?
-Yes.
-Do you think they know everything?
-I feel the cops know everything.
-Honestly, I felt like they don't know.
-They knew who was which number.
-I think they'll get everything right.
They'll get everything right.
They seemed unsure though.
So, let me explain it to you.
They seemed unsure to you,
because you were definitely
not a criminal.
-What does that mean?
-You're a Good Citizen or the Madman.
-That's what they thought?
-[Dail] That's why they seemed unsure.
No, it's not me.
[Horseking] Seriously, Yang Dail
kept accusing me from the very beginning.
He looked like a madman when he said,
"You're the Madman, aren't you?"
That's how he was,
so I was really annoyed.
I don't believe this guy. It's not true.
ASSAULT CRIMINAL TEAM
-Wait.
-I'm sure.
PANI BOTTLE TAKES JAEGYUN SOMEWHERE
-[Pani Bottle] Really?
-[Jaegyun] Yes.
Which one of the two do you think it is?
-[Jaegyun] Who?
-Between Dail and Horseking.
I just wanted to trust Dail,
-so I thought it was Horseking.
-[Pani Bottle] Right.
But I really don't know right now.
-Well, no one does.
-Right.
We need to discuss altogether anyway.
-We do.
Well, the main issue is
we don't know who the Good Citizens
and the Madman are here.
We need to decide who's a Good Citizen...
-And who's the Madman.
-...and who's the Madman.
We need to decide that.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
-[Pani Bottle] Can we talk for a moment?
-[Jaegyun] Wait. This is so sudden. Geez.
Wait, why do you keep having
private conversations?
You're not on the same team.
It's because we're not on the same team.
I don't get it.
We need to look on our own teams...
YANG DAIL GETS IRRITATED
It's because we all have
shared information.
[Dail] This is throwing me off.
They're confusing me at the very end.
[Dail] It was almost time to vote,
but he chose to talk to someone else
instead of me.
How do you think that makes me feel?
"What's this?"
"This guy is suspecting me."
[Pani Bottle] We wanted
to ask you something too.
Did Horseking really try
to show you his card?
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
-Did he show you or try to?
He tried to show it, but I stopped him.
ROUND 1 PRISON
You're not supposed to show it.
HORSEKING ALMOST SHOWED HIS PROFILE CARD
[Pani Bottle] Damn, I'm completely lost.
I feel like it's fifty-fifty right now.
-It's driving me crazy.
-I know. [sighs]
[Pani Bottle] This is driving me crazy.
[sighs deeply]
-What?
-[Jaegyun] Nothing.
[Pani Bottle] I mean, it's odd.
No matter how clueless one is,
if people see "Good Citizen" on your card,
that would be a disaster.
Yet he tried to show it?
When I heard that,
I started thinking,
"Maybe he's not the traitor."
From that point on,
since he'd been making aggressive claims,
I started suspecting Dail.
He seemed a bit strange.
He was getting worked up
and started to make me slowly think,
"Is he the Madman?"
[sighs deeply]
They made this God damn game well.
Can I talk to Horseking first?
-Sure.
-Yes.
[Horseking] About what?
-Seriously, why is this confusing you?
-[Joonsu] Listen...
[sighs]
Either way, we have to pick
one of two people.
-I just need to decide that.
-To me, it seems like...
[whispers] Yang Dail is the Madman.
[♪ tense music playing]
I hate to say this,
but I'm suspicious of you too.
I can't really...
If you can't even trust me,
we're out of options.
I'm going to vote for Dail as the Madman.
We have to go with that.
I see. I get it.
Okay, okay.
Dail.
Shouldn't the two of us talk?
Dail, have a talk with me too.
No, let's all talk together.
[Pani Bottle]
We'll talk after you two finish.
-No, let's talk together.
-[Pani Bottle] What's the point of that?
-It's someone among us three.
-But I think...
VOICES GRADUALLY GET LOUDER
-I think we can talk together.
-[Pani Bottle] I'll let you talk first.
Dail kept insisting
that the three of us should talk.
But I wanted to talk one-on-one.
You have to talk one-on-one
to understand what's going on.
But he kept saying
the three of us should talk together.
That felt even more suspicious.
Here's the thing.
From the very beginning,
I trusted Pani Bottle completely.
But toward the end,
I felt like I made a mistake.
What's going on?
That's not it. Anyhow, I think...
It's so easy to get this one right.
[Pani Bottle] I need
to listen to them first.
[sighs] This is hard.
[Dail] Guys, I'm...
-Guys, I'm going to vote.
-[Pani Bottle] Okay.
-Right now?
-Wait...
YANG DAIL SUDDENLY GOES TO CAST HIS VOTE
[sighs]
[dealer] Hello.
Please vote to identify the traitor.
VIOLENT CRIMES BURGLAR
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-[sighs] This isn't it.
-[dealer] Mr. Pani Bottle.
Write down the person you suspect
with a special role.
[Horseking] I chose Yang Dail.
-Hello.
-[dealer] Hello, Kim Ddolddol.
GOOD CITIZEN KIM DDOLDDOL
[Ddolddol] I hope
the detectives get it right.
CI TEAM
GOOD CITIZEN: JAEGYUN
[Ddolddol] Joonsu has complete faith in me
so I'm not worried at all.
Please, please, please.
[Jimin] It's possible that Jieun
was just really good at acting.
Maybe she tricked me?
Seriously...
[♪ suspenseful music intensifies]
[host] The Main Match,
"Cops and Robbers," has ended.
All players,
please gather in the Main Hall.
[sighs]
I can't trust anyone now.
-[Jieun] Oh, my God. I want to go home.
-[Dail] I can't trust anyone.
[host] It's time to reveal
the identities of all the players.
COPS MUST IDENTIFY
THE CRIMINALS' TRUE IDENTITIES
BURGLAR 1, 2, 3
ASSAULT 1, 2, 3, DRUG 1, 2, 3
JAEGYUN, DDOLDDOL, JOONSU
PANI BOTTLE, HORSEKING, DAIL
JIEUN, JIMIN, ZZONE
We got it.
We got it right.
ASIDE FROM THE SPECIAL ROLES,
THEY GUESSED THE CRIMINALS CORRECTLY
[gasps] The cops got it right.
THE ONLY MYSTERY LEFT IS THE SPECIAL ROLES
[host] Among the criminals,
the first Good Citizen is...
[♪ tense music playing]
[Jimin] It was really confusing.
[Ddolddol] I was confident
I wouldn't be caught.
[host] The first Good Citizen is...
Kim Ddolddol.
FIRST GOOD CITIZEN IS KIM DDOLDDOL
CI TEAM'S ASSIGNED TRAITOR: BURGLAR 2
CI TEAM'S ASSIGNED TRAITOR: KIM DDOLDDOL
What?
[♪ dramatic music playing]
We were doomed from Round 1.
[groans]
Ddolddol. Ddolddol!
I'm sorry.
I trusted him so much.
[Joonsu] My biggest mistake
was trusting Ddolddol too much.
That's when I realized it.
"Right. This is a survival game."
Everyone is my enemy.
I'm definitely going to get back
at Ddolddol and betray him.
I can't just sit back and take it.
[host] We will reveal
the second Good Citizen.
LAST GOOD CITIZEN CANDIDATE
IS FROM VIOLENT CRIMES OR NARCOTICS
The Good Citizen is...
ASSAULT CRIMINAL 2
THE GOOD CITIZEN
Horseking.
[groans]
It was Horseking.
[gasps]
[Pani Bottle gasps]
[dealer] You are Assault Criminal 2.
Also, you are a Good Citizen.
[gasps] Me?
My strategy was
to not play the role as a Good Citizen.
I was going to act like a regular criminal
to fool both the cops and the criminals.
-I don't have a map.
-[Jimin] Didn't you see the clues?
Hey, they're all in here.
PRETENDING TO NOT UNDERSTAND
I acted as if I was clueless.
I pretended I couldn't do anything.
And as a criminal on the run,
I did my best.
But I also decided to get physical
and get my hands dirty.
ROUND 1 CHASE
ROUND 2 CHASE
I didn't want to be suspected
as a Good Citizen.
Jaegyun said he saw it.
I think that kind of helped.
Didn't Jaegyun say
he saw me on the ground?
USING JAEGYUN'S WITNESS ACCOUNT
Then, Jaegyun gave the tip.
As for the Drug Criminal team,
it's likely Jieun and Jimin.
You think Dail is an Assault Criminal?
He told me he's an Assault Criminal,
and he's Assault Criminal 3.
[Horseking] I shared some helpful intel
based on what I knew.
I gave them tips.
Seriously...
[Dail] I'm such an idiot.
If I had stuck to my guns
and written Horseking at the end,
I wouldn't have felt this dumb afterward.
I ended up voting for Pani Bottle,
so I feel like even more of an idiot.
VIOLENT CRIMES
GOOD CITIZEN: PANI BOTTLE
TRAITOR VOTE
DAIL CHOSE PANI BOTTLE
Why is he suspecting me?
At first, I couldn't understand it.
I thought it was ridiculous.
Then, I got thrown off.
"Wait a minute."
Does that mean
when Horseking was acting clueless,
it was actually real...
and was Pani Bottle lying
from the beginning?
I shouldn't have let it happen,
but I wavered.
[groans, clicks tongue]
[Pani Bottle] Where did it all go wrong?
I realized I'd made the wrong choice.
CI TEAM
GOOD CITIZEN: YANG DAIL
TRAITOR VOTE
PANI BOTTLE CHOSE DAIL
-Horseking was so good.
-But now...
[host] And finally,
we will reveal the Madman.
ALL THAT REMAINS IS TO CATCH THE MADMAN
FROM THE DRUG CRIMINALS TEAM
[Jimin] I didn't suspect Jieun at all.
[host] On the Drug Criminal team,
the Madman is...
Drug Criminal 3, ZZONE is the Madman.
DRUG CRIMINALS IDENTIFY THE MADMAN
[both chuckle]
I told you to trust me.
[Jieun] It was my own strategy.
I actually had no idea if ZZONE
was a Good Citizen or the Madman.
In the interrogation room...
Did you catch all the Drug Criminals?
Aren't they Jimin and ZZONE?
I pretended to be a Good Citizen
to see how they'd react.
Among the Drug Criminals...
no one gave you tips, right?
No.
Is it you?
A Good Citizen's role is to help the cops.
But there was no one.
So, the answer is clear.
The Madman is definitely on our team.
[ZZONE] I was disappointed.
I'm supposed to pretend to be a criminal.
[groans] I'm going nuts.
How do I pull off the Madman?
Looking back,
things could have turned out differently
if I had acted a little smarter.
[host] The Narcotics cop...
Why did she ask me this?
She asked if anyone helped us at the end.
Jieun thought there was a Good Citizen
among the Drug Criminals.
-She was trying to find them.
-[Eunsil] Okay.
[Sanghyun]
Because she's not a Good Citizen.
-She's a criminal.
I think that's why. It's not her.
SANGHYUN IDENTIFIED JIEUN'S INTENT
It's not Jieun.
[Eunsil] When I talked to Jimin,
it seemed like
she didn't want to get arrested.
That made me think
she's just a regular criminal.
ZZONE might be the Madman.
[host] The Narcotics cop
successfully caught the criminal.
JIEUN AND JIMIN ARE ARRESTED
[Eunsil] It felt so good. I felt so proud.
NARCOTICS UNIT
JIEUN, JIMIN, ZZONE
SUCCESSFULLY CAPTURED THE MADMAN
[host] In Deadly Tag's first match,
"Cops and Robbers,"
the winners are...
Youn Sanghyun...
Yuk Junseo...
Jang Eunsil...
[all gasp]
ALL THREE COPS SUCCEEDED
[host] Shin Jieun...
Kim Ddolddol...
[player gasps]
Horseking...
[players exclaim]
and Park Jimin.
FOUR CRIMINALS SUCCEEDED
-Nice, nice.
-Where's Horseking?
He was unbelievable.
[Horseking] It felt great.
If I keep this momentum up,
I might be able to win.
Like this.
I want to dance like this.
VICTORY DANCE
But I thought I'd look uncool,
so I quietly sat back down.
[host] Winners, please take
your prize money of 20 million won
and your Elimination Immunity Passes.
[dealer] Here is your 20 million won
and Elimination Immunity Pass.
Your 20 million won
will be kept in your personal locker.
It was a perfect day today.
[host] And the losers are...
Hwang Jaegyun...
Lee Joonsu...
Pani Bottle...
Yang Dail...
and ZZONE.
[Dail sighs]
All I can do is sigh.
[Pani Bottle] I feel like
I lost so helplessly.
The disappointment and defeat
all came crashing down on me.
[host] In Deadly Tag,
elimination candidates
will be decided through a vote.
Players without
Elimination Immunity Passes
are subject to the Elimination Vote.
All players,
please choose two players
to send to the Death Match
and cast your vote.
Additional votes cost 20 million won each.
This transaction is only available
in the Dealer Room during voting time.
Also, players may transfer funds
between each other,
but all transactions must take place
in the presence of a Dealer.
Voting will close in an hour.
VOTING BEGINS
[timer beeping]
[players chattering indistinctly]
-I showed everything to you, Pani Bottle.
-I know.
I do admit that I got confused.
But when you picked me,
I had no other choice.
-[Dail] Right.
-Isn't that true?
But this is what I thought.
You completely ignored me.
But that's actually not true.
I said I wanted to talk to you at the end.
I needed to talk with people,
so I called whoever was nearby.
I was going to talk to you,
but you suddenly wouldn't talk to me.
That's because we talked first
from the very beginning.
Then, the order should be--
Honestly, the order doesn't matter.
That's how I saw it.
You became suspicious of me
even though I'd been honest with you.
Then, everything I thought I knew
about you started to change.
Well, it's easy to say so in hindsight.
[sighs] I handed him everything,
but Pani Bottle didn't utilize it at all,
and I felt so frustrated.
It made my blood boil.
[sighs]
Dail, let's work together
to get the Immunity Pass.
We need to survive this.
[Joonsu] I just needed to survive this.
Horseking, let's go talk.
A SUDDEN REQUEST TO TALK
Why all of a sudden?
Is this how it usually goes?
We always have to go off and talk?
JOONSU TAKES ACTION FIRST
You have to help me this time.
Please help me.
I'm so scared.
I won't vote you out,
because I promised to help you.
For real.
ASKS WITH AN INNOCENT SMILE
Please help me out just this once.
I really need your help.
Thank you.
[Joonsu] Since I'm the youngest,
I'm kind of in a position
where I get a lot of love.
I always smile when I talk.
It looks like Joonsu
is going around buying votes.
-[Jaegyun] I know.
-Should I do something too?
Geez.
OTHER ELIMINATION CANDIDATES GET MOVING
Eunsil, you know, right?
We don't attack our allies.
[all chuckle]
[Eunsil] Since I'm friends with Dail,
I wasn't thinking about voting for him.
Junseo, you know, right?
I helped you from the very beginning.
BRIEF BUT BIG HELP
-Remember?
-Yes, I do.
-Ddolddol.
-Yes?
You tricked me, Ddolddol.
Ddolddol, you tricked me once.
You can't do it twice.
[exclaims]
[ZZONE] It felt a little embarrassing
to ask directly,
but I couldn't get eliminated.
-Please don't pick me. Help me out.
-Sure, I don't think you will.
Please help me out.
-For real...
-[Sanghyun] Why?
-Why?
-[ZZONE] Why?
[Dail whispers] Joonsu.
Let's vote her out.
-Okay.
-Let's vote ZZONE out.
PLOTTING TO ELIMINATE ZZONE
So, we know one person will be ZZONE.
And Pani Bottle told us to vote him out.
PANI BOTTLE GAVE UP?
[sighs deeply]
[Pani Bottle] I'll go.
-What?
-[Pani Bottle] I'll go.
[Pani Bottle] I don't deserve to be here.
Personally, I felt quite defeated.
I was determined
not to go through that defeat again.
I felt like going into the Death Match,
winning it, and surviving
was the only way to overcome this.
I'll get voted out.
And you vote for one more person.
That's not right.
TRYING TO STOP PANI BOTTLE
No, don't do that.
Let's leave it to the vote.
You did nothing wrong.
-[ZZONE] Exactly.
-[Pani Bottle] I did. But anyway...
Then, we'll vote for Pani Bottle
and ZZONE.
Or we could each buy one extra vote
and vote for those people.
[Joonsu] You want to buy one to be safe?
We could do that.
-Then, that's two votes for each of us.
-That's right.
PROMISE TO BUY EXTRA VOTES
TO PICK ZZONE & PANI BOTTLE
-Let's stick together and not lie.
-Sure. I don't lie.
You really won't lie to me?
I told Joonsu we'd spend our money
to each buy an extra vote
to vote out ZZONE.
Pani Bottle volunteered to go
to the Death Match,
and he wanted us to vote him out.
He wanted to get voted out...
So I mean, there's no reason not to.
[Jaegyun sighs] I don't know what to do.
[Dail] We have no choice
but to vote for Pani Bottle.
Let's go to the back.
[Jaegyun] Who else do you want to pick?
-There's no other option.
-ZZONE?
[Dail] That's what Joonsu and I agreed on.
Okay.
Dail suggested we all vote for one person.
I got promises from Jaegyun and Joonsu,
so we'd each spend 20 million won
to each have two votes.
[dealer] Would you like
to buy extra votes?
Yes.
There's nothing I can do.
PANI BOTTLE
ZZONE
-An additional vote costs 20 million won.
-Okay.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
PANI BOTTLE, ZZONE
What will you do?
The safe bet would be
someone who's good at survival games
and likely to last a long time.
Right.
HORSEKING THINKS THE STRONG
SHOULD BE GONE
Junseo.
Do you think we should vote out
people who are good at games?
For me...
I see it differently.
If you trap someone,
they might have no choice
but to strike back
at the opposing side.
That's why.
The idea of eliminating
the strongest player
feels a bit one-dimensional.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATE VOTE
PANI BOTTLE, ZZONE
YUK JUNSEO PICKED ZZONE
CURRENT VOTING TOTALS
PANI BOTTLE 5 VOTES, DAIL 0 VOTES
ZZONE 5 VOTES
JAEGYUN 0 VOTES, JOONSU 0 VOTES
[sighs] Should I buy extra votes or not?
DAIL, JAEGYUN
ZZONE VOTED FOR YANG DAIL
AND HWANG JAEGYUN
This is so heartbreaking.
There's nothing I can do.
[host] Voting has closed.
We will announce the results.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Here are the voting results.
The player with the most votes is...
Pani Bottle.
[Pani Bottle] Just as I expected.
[host] The next
Death Match candidate is...
Yang Dail.
[gasps]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Dail] I couldn't believe it.
It was unbelievable.
If Joonsu and Jaegyun
had kept their promises,
I likely wouldn't have been picked.
One of these bastards broke their promise.
As I realized that, I thought,
"You can't trust these damn people."
RESULTS
PANI BOTTLE 12 VOTES, DAIL 7 VOTES
ZZONE 5 VOTES,
JAEGYUN 4 VOTES, JOONSU 0 VOTES
That's a relief.
[Joonsu] I think everything was...
thanks to Jimin.
30 MINUTES AGO
Can you come here for a moment?
I have something to tell you.
One vote costs 20 million won.
If you give us 10 million won each,
that's two votes.
ASKING FOR 10 MILLION WON PER PERSON
IN EXCHANGE FOR HELP
But if I say no, you're going to pick me.
This isn't right.
Just don't vote for me.
DAIL REJECTS JIMIN'S OFFER
I'm begging you.
Well, that's...
It's not easy to buy two votes
with 10 million won.
But Dail wouldn't trust me.
From that point on,
I thought it'd be better
if he got eliminated.
Can you help me out just one time?
JOONSU APPROACHES WITH A SMILE
[Jimin] Joonsu slowly came over
and asked me not to vote him out.
But I couldn't do it for free.
We just met.
Then, if you give me and Jieun
10 million won each,
you can get two votes
for the price of one.
IMMEDIATELY ACCEPTS
-Okay, I'll ask.
-Okay. Thank you.
I needed someone on my side
who I could trust.
Jieun and I had built a bond
from winning together.
This was good news.
If Joonsu gives Jieun and me
10 million won each to vote,
it's good for Joonsu, me, and Jieun.
Three birds, one stone, right?
And Joonsu can't be eliminated.
He is such a useful asset.
[inhales sharply]
I wanted to keep him around.
[dealer] You have transferred
10 million won to Shin Jieun.
-To Park Jimin...
-10 million won.
-Yes, 10 million won.
-[dealer] 10 million won.
Rather than paying
20 million won for one vote,
giving 10 million won each
would be a win-win for both sides.
PANI BOTTLE
DAIL
[Jimin] I picked Pani Bottle
and the one who turned down my offer.
Yang Dail.
And when taking off the belt earlier,
ZZONE helped me.
I wanted to at least
do something to help her.
[Jimin] The one who may be difficult
to compete against later on is Dail.
Okay. Dail and...
[Joonsu] At first, I was going to pick
ZZONE and Pani Bottle,
but Jimin told me to pick Yang Dail
because he's strong.
So I thought,
"Well, as long as it's not me
and as long as I survive, it's okay."
So I picked him.
ENDS UP BETRAYING DAIL
There's nothing I can do.
[Jimin] It was a great plan.
EVERYTHING GOES AS SHE HAD PLANNED
[host] Yang Dail and Pani Bottle,
please exit the Main Hall immediately.
-Win and come back to us.
-[laughs]
Go out there and win.
It wasn't me. Seriously, go and win.
-I really hope you win.
-Had I known you'd do this,
I wouldn't have talked to you.
-[Pani Bottle] I...
-Let's go.
-[Pani Bottle] I didn't vote for you.
-[Dail] Let's go. I picked you.
-[Pani Bottle] Because I told you to.
-I picked you.
ELIMINATION CANDIDATES
PANI BOTTLE, YANG DAIL
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Jieun] This is crazy.
[Jieun and Jaegyun laugh]
It's freezing.
THE SURVIVORS ARRIVE AT THE LODGING
-[ZZONE gasps]
-Isn't that a pool?
[gasps]
-[Joonsu] You want to jump straight in?
-Can we go in there?
[Jieun] This is crazy.
Is this where food is?
-[Jimin] This is insane.
-[Jieun] I'm hungry. I see ramyeon.
DINING ROOM
[Jimin] This must be the Main Hall.
MAIN HALL
VOTING ROOM
ROOM 1 ON FIRST FLOOR
ROOM 2 ON FIRST FLOOR
ROOM ON SECOND FLOOR,
When I saw the house,
it felt like, "I've survived."
But knowing this could end up
being my grave,
I wasn't sure how I should've felt.
We'll take the second floor
since we're younger.
-I think the rooms might have an effect.
-Right.
[Horseking] This feels strange.
ALL SURVIVING PLAYERS HAVE CHECKED IN
[Dail] Geez, from the first day...
Fucking hell.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
What's this?
[exclaims]
[chuckles]
PRISON
-She's been here all along.
-[Pani Bottle] Gyeong Sujin?
A FEW HOURS AGO
[Sujin] I knew this would happen. [sighs]
What is this?
Am I a prisoner?
You've got to be kidding me.
[Sujin] I really have to wear
a prison uniform?
It actually made me...
more determined.
I thought...
"Just you wait and see how I get out."
Just watch.
So I made sure to eat well...
and build up my strength.
SUJIN WAS MOTIVATED BUT THEN GOT DRAINED
[Dail] This is going to be fun.
THE ELIMINATION CANDIDATES MEET IN PRISON
[Pani Bottle] This is great.
[mic feedback]
[host] Everyone,
please gather in the Main Hall.
-[Eunsil] Hello.
-[Jieun] Hi.
-You're looking good.
-What?
-You look happy.
-I slept well.
[Jaegyun] No wonder.
[mic feedback]
[host] Congratulations to everyone
who survived the first Main Match.
We will now begin the first Seeker Vote.
What?
-Seeker?
-[Jieun] What?
-Seeker Vote?
[Horseking] It turns out
there's a Seeker. [gasps]
[Eunsil] What's going on?
[host] The Seeker is a hidden architect
who creates chaos and controls
the course of the chase,
secretly working
to prevent the players from winning.
[exhales]
[Jieun gasps] Damn, this is insane.
[Sanghyun] There's a Seeker here
all of a sudden?
[sighs]
[Jaegyun] I couldn't process it
for a moment.
[Horseking] We were fooled.
They played us from the start.
I don't know. I can't trust anything.
Yeah, it's boring to just play games.
[Jimin] This is going to be
really interesting.
Someone has been fooling us.
LAST NIGHT, WHILE EVERYONE WAS ASLEEP
SOMEONE WAS MOVING IN SECRET
[host] The Seeker Room has opened.
DEADLY TAG
RULES
[dealer] Seeker [bleep],
select a player for elimination.
[distorted voice 1]
It was really thrilling.
[distorted voice 2] If you stand out,
you'll get eliminated fast.
[host] We will begin the Seeker Vote.
[Jimin] What's going on?
[Horseking] It turns out there's a Seeker.
[Jaegyun] Someone has been fooling us.
[Dail] You can't trust these damn people.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Jieun] Are you the Seeker?
[Jaegyun] The Seeker's doing
something here right now.
[Jimin] They create chaos
and control how the game goes.
[Jieun] This is all the Seeker's doing?
[Pani Bottle] I was going crazy.
That God damn ridiculous Seeker.
[Horseking]
The Seeker's playing us right now.
I'm so pissed off.
[Pani Bottle] Fuck!
[Jimin] Shit, who is it?
[Seeker] Can you find me?
Catch me if you can.
[Junseo] Catch them!
[Pani Bottle] Do it now!
-It's okay! Go!
-[ZZONE] When did it switch?
I never did that.
What are you talking about?
[ZZONE] Hang on!
What's with you?
It's just us. Why can't you talk?
If you confuse me,
I'll accuse you of being the Seeker.
We could've eliminated them, so why...
[Jimin] Let's eliminate the strongest one.
[Jieun] I didn't want
to get eliminated first.
[Jimin] It'll be fucking hard
to play together.
[Pani Bottle groans]
I should rip out all that pink hair.
[Sujin] Did I really do
something that bad?
[sobbing]
[Pani Bottle] This game fucking sucks.
[Seeker] I guess you'll have to go. Bye.
[♪ mysterious music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim